arbitragepro.com 2008-06-16

# Arbitrage Pro: Privacy Policy - sports arbitrage, arbitrage arb service, arbitrage arb software, arbitrage arb trading, arb finder, arbs, no risk, zero risk, sports arb

**_A. Information We Collect_**  
**Required Information**  
To open a Arbitrage Pro Limited account, you must provide your name, address, e-mail address and credit card or debit card information. 

**Transaction Information**  
When you use Arbitrage Pro Limited, we retain this information for each of your transactions and we also collect the Internet address (IP address) of the computer or device you use to access your Arbitrage Pro Limited account. 

**Web Site Traffic Information**  
Because of the way that World Wide Web communication standards work, when you arrive at or leave the Arbitrage Pro Limited Web site, we automatically receive the Web address of the site that you came from or are going to. We also collect information on which pages of our Web site you visit while you are on the Arbitrage Pro Limited site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our Web site. We use this information only to try to understand our customers' preferences better and to manage the load on our servers, so as to improve our service and your experience with Arbitrage Pro Limited. We do not track the Web sites that you visit before or after you leave the Arbitrage Pro Limited site. 

**Our Use of "Cookies"**  
"Cookies" are small files of data that reside on your computer and allow us to recognize you as a Arbitrage Pro Limited customer if you return to the Arbitrage Pro Limited site using the same computer and browser. We send a "session cookie" to your computer if and when you log in to your Arbitrage Pro Limited account by entering your user name and password. These cookies allow us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages in our site during the same session, so that you don't need to re-enter your password multiple times. Once you log out or close your browser, these session cookies expire and no longer have any effect. 

We also use longer-lasting cookies to remember your login details for a period of one month, so that you don't have to retype your username and password each time you want to log in to your Arbitrage Pro Limited account. Our cookie files are encoded so that your username and password can only be interpreted by Arbitrage Pro Limited. 

**Customer Service Correspondence**  
If you send us correspondence, including e-mails and faxes, we retain such information in the records of your account. We will also retain customer service correspondence and other correspondence from Arbitrage Pro Limited to you. We retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and violations of our User Agreement. We may, over time, delete these records if permitted by law. 

**_B. Our Use and Disclosure of Information_**  
**Internal Uses**  
We collect, store and process your personal information on servers located in the United States. We use the information we collect about you in order 1) to provide our services and process your transactions, 2) to provide customer service, and 3) to improve our products and services. 

We give access to individually identifiable information about our users only to those employees who require it to fulfil customer service requests. 

**Disclosure to Third Parties Other Than Arbitrage Pro Limited Customers**  
Arbitrage Pro Limited will not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information to third parties. Arbitrage Pro Limited will not share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties except in the limited circumstances described below, or with your express permission. These third parties are limited by law or by contract from using the information for secondary purposes beyond the purposes for which the information is shared. 

  1. We share information with companies that help us process the transactions you request and protect our customers' transactions from fraud, such as sharing your credit card number with a service that screens for lost and stolen card numbers. Additionally, if you go into a negative balance and owe us money, we may share information with processing companies including collection agencies. 
  2. We disclose information that we in good faith believe is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of illegal activity, or to conduct investigations of violations of our User Agreement. We disclose information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process, including subpoenas from private parties in a civil action. 
  3. We disclose information to your agent or legal representative (such as the holder of a power of attorney that you grant, or a guardian appointed for you). 
  4. As with any other business, it is possible that Arbitrage Pro Limited in the future could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by Arbitrage Pro Limited, including customer account information, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy unless and until it is amended. 

**Our Contacts with Arbitrage Pro Limited Customers**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis via e-mail to provide requested services. We use your e-mail address to confirm your opening of an Arbitrage Pro Limited account, to send information about important changes to our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures required by law. Generally, users cannot opt out of these communications, but they will be primarily informational in nature rather than promotional. 

In connection with independent audits of our financial statements and operations, the auditors may seek to contact a sample of our customers to confirm that our records are accurate. However, these auditors cannot use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Internet Address Information**  
We use IP addresses, browser types and access times to analyze trends, administer the site, improve site performance and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

**_C. Information Security_**  
**Information Security**  
Arbitrage Pro Limited is committed to handling your information with high standards of information security. Your credit card information is stored only in encrypted form. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. 

The security of your Arbitrage Pro Limited account also relies on your protection of your Arbitrage Pro Limited password. You may not share your Arbitrage Pro Limited password with anyone. Arbitrage Pro Limited will never ask you to send your password or other sensitive information to us in an e-mail, though we may ask you to enter this type of information on the Arbitrage Pro Limited website.
